<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">MTG Pro Land Assistant</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="deck_text">Size of the deck</string>
    <string name="usable_sources"># of mana  sources</string>
    <string name="by_turn">by turn</string>
    <string name="achieve_chance">Rate of success (Try 84.5)</string>
    <string name="button_submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="button_help">Help</string>
    <string name="button_reset">Reset</string>
    <string name="title_activity_display_message">Results</string>
    <string name="title_activity_help_page">Help Page</string>
    <string name="description">
        
        Simply fill in the form above and press Submit to perform a calculation!\n\n
        If this is your first time using this app and you do not understand, try the help page!
        
	</string>
    <string name="help_message">
        
        Every person who plays Magic: The Gathering has run out of mana at one point. Whether 
		
		you\'re one short of playing that powerful creature or have an island when you need a 
		
		mountain to play a counter spell, it\'s something that is hard to avoid in M:TG… until now. 
		
		Using complex algorithms of probability and hypergeometric calculations, this assistant 
		
		will tell you exactly how many lands — and what type of lands — to put in your deck to 
		
		cast a certain card on a certain turn. While it is hard to understand at first, using this 
		
		application is the MOST accurate way to make a deck with the BEST results.\n\n
		
		How to use this application:\n\n
		
		1. Create a scenario.\n
		
		Say you are in the process of building a black/blue deck. Your best friend loves to 
		
		use plenty of spells against you, so you want to be able to use "Cancel" as soon as 
		
		possible. "Cancel" costs two blue mana and one colorless mana to cost, so you would 
		
		only be able to cast it on turn three at the earliest. In this scenario, your goal is to put the 
		
		best amount of mana in your deck so that the probability of having three mana on the 
		
		field, two of them being blue, is very high. Create a similar scenario for your deck. 
		
		Choose a card and the turn you want to cast it by. Only choose a card that you 
		
		ABSOLUTELY want to ensure is played, something that is very important to your deck 
		
		mechanics.\n\n
		
		2. Find the total amount of land for your deck.\n
		
		There is a good chance you will have to do multiple calculations with this 
		
		assistant. The card "Cancel" requires two calculations — one to ensure you have the blue 
		
		mana required and one to ensure you have three mana total.\n
		
		 For the first calculation, you will find the total mana needed in your deck. On the main 
		
		page, you would plug in four numbers: The number of cards in your deck (60), the 
		
		number of mana sources needed (3), the turn you want to be able to cast the spell (3), 
		
		and the probability you have the cards (84.5). The higher the probability, the better 
		
		chance you have the cards. We recommend 84.5; that means that out of every ten games 
		
		you play, statistically eight and a half of them will allow you to cast this spell. Higher 
		
		numbers than that can throw other cards off-balance and increase the amount of land in 
		
		your deck.\n
		
		So, you hit submit and get your results. 26 untapped lands and 0 tapped lands, 26 
		
		untapped lands and 1 tapped land, 26 untapped lands and 2 tapped lands… the list goes on. 
		
		What does this mean?\n
		
		You searched for the total cost to play "Cancel", three sources of mana, regardless of 
		
		color. So these numbers refer to the total amount of land that should be in your deck.
		
		"Untapped" lands refer to lands that can be tapped as a mana source the same turn that 
		
		they are first played. This is basic land; mountains, islands, swamps, etc. "Tapped" lands 
		
		refer to lands that come out on the field tapped and cannot be used until the turn after 
		
		they are first played, like Guildgates. So, the calculator says that to cast "Cancel" at least 
		
		84.5 percent of the time, you need 26 lands total if only using basic land and 27+ lands if using 
		
		certain special lands that cannot be utilized the first turn they appear.\n\n
		
		3. Find the amount(s) of specific colored land for your deck.\n
		
		Now that you have your total land, how many of those need to be blue? 
		
		Go back to the main calculator screen. Input the amount of cards in your deck (60), 
		
		but change the amount of sources needed to 2 to reflect the 2 blue mana necessary to 
		
		cast "Cancel". The turn (3) and probability (84.5) stay the same. After pressing submit, 
		
		you get: 19 untapped lands and 0 tapped lands, 18 untapped lands and 1 tapped land, and 17 
		
		untapped lands and 2 tapped lands… so on and so forth. This means that 19 of those 26 -
		
		27 lands should be blue to ensure the 84.5 percent success rate of casting "Cancel" on the third 
		
		turn.\n
		
		With cards that have multiple colors, repeat this step for each color. For a card using red 
		
		and white mana, you would perform three calculations. You would perform step two and 
		
		then perform step three twice — one for red and white. This works with any amount of 
		
		colors and any combination.
        
	</string>

</resources>